{
    "id": "c9d7166916ec4d02a96ac70f2a80eb45",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Don’t forget to signal ……………………. turning right.",
            "description": "It is possible to leave out subject + be after when or while. The above sentence can also be written as:\r\nDon’t forget to signal when you are turning right.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "while",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I decided to stop and rest ……………………. I was feeling tired.",
            "description": "For can be used to give the reason for something. It is more common in a formal style.",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "for",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. I was feeling hungry, I decided to have lunch.",
            "description": "A for clause can never come at the beginning of a sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "Because",
                "For",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She was acting …………………….. she was the boss.",
            "description": "As if and as though mean the same. They are used to say what a situation seems like.",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You look …………………… you know each other.",
            "description": "We use as though to say what a situation seems like.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "though",
                "as though"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It seems ……………………… it is going to rain.",
            "description": "Like is possible here in an informal style.",
            "answers": [
                "as if",
                "as though",
                "like",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "I will remember that experience ………………………… I live.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "as soon as",
                "no longer than"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You can stay in my home …………………….. you do not disturb me.",
            "description": "All of these expressions can be used to express a condition.",
            "answers": [
                "as long as",
                "so long as",
                "on condition that",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "There was a big argument about …………………… we should close the shop.",
            "description": "Only whether is possible after prepositions.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not sure ……………………… I will be able to come.",
            "description": "Both whether and if can be used to introduce indirect Yes/No questions.",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t decide ………………………. to wait or leave.",
            "description": "Only whether is possible before a to-infinitive.",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… I will come I am not sure at the moment.",
            "description": "When an indirect question comes at the beginning of the sentence, we use whether.",
            "answers": [
                "Whether",
                "If",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}